Now, these people done lost their minds.
They talk about slavery benefited black people.
The effort that is being put forth to straight up lie is one that we really just can't ignore.
OK, because they focused.
We're focused, too, which is why I want to let you know about a very important event going down July 30th to August 3rd.
The African-American Policy Forum is hosting its fourth annual Critical Race Theory Summer School titled Fighting Back to Move Forward, Defending the Freedom to Learn.
So if you want to defend your freedom to learn, your freedom to read, don't forget it used to be against the law.
They trying to bring us back there. Then you need to go right now to aapf.org backslash CRT Summer School.
This is going to be a whole bunch of smart black folks talk about a whole bunch of smart black things that we all need to know.
See you there.